# AJAY KUMAR KHIMAJIBHAI SINGAL

Sarvoday Society Haripar Road , Dhrangadhra-363310 Dist-Surendranagar Gujarat Mobile number:- +91 90992 51528 Email:- ajayraj885@gmail.com

### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

To work at the credible position in the well established company And get the ambitious opportunity to utilize my knowledge and experience in the professional organization and do my very best in keeping the reputation of the company high.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Maruti Suzuki NEXA Dream Vehicles Surendranagar

Relationship Manager

15/12/2016 - Till date

Direct sales to Customer. Lead Generate. Target achievement. Fulfill customer need.

## Varmora foods pvt Ltd Ahmedabad

Admin executive

01/09/2015 - 30/10/2016

Routine office work. Generate Invoice. Maintain Raw material and Finish goods material details.

### Concept Hyundai Surendranagar

Sales executive

12/11/2013 - 30/10/2014

Direct sales to Customer. Need of assement of customer. Lead Generate. Target achievement.

#### **EDUCATION**

### GUJARAT University

B.A in English literature with 46% 2013

#### G.S.H.S.E.B

H.S.C with 48% 2009

# • G.S.H.S.E.B

S.S.C with 45% 2007

#### PERSONAL STRENGTHS

Positive Attitude. Believe in Smart work and Hard work. Good Communication skill. Quick learner.

### PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth : 11/11/1991

Marital Status: Married

Nationality : Indian

Languages

: English, Hindi, Gujarati Known

: Music. Reading Novel. Watching Movies. Going for Long Hobbies

drive on Car.

AJAY KUMAR KHIMAJIBHAI SINGAL